

@

dishali.khilari12@gmail.com

0413065691

0

Sydney, NSW 2000

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/i n/dishali-khilari-58729b145/

EDUCATION

Master of Science: Information Technology And Computer Networks. **Charles Sturt University**, Brisbane, Australia., Australia, November 2020

- Elected for Tutoring as PASS Leader in 2019.
- Received Scholarship from CSU.
- Awarded Completion of STRIVE Leadership Program.
- Member of Student Representative Committee.
- Majored in Information **Technology and Computer** Network.

Bachelor of Science: **Computer Engineering** L.T.C.O.E, Mumbai, India, India, June 2015

· Graduated with 5 GPA.

Diploma: Computer Engineering Technology S. H. Jondhale Polytechnic, Mumbai, India., India, June 2012

- · Graduated with 6 GPA
- Awarded 3rd price in inter-college essay writing competition.

S.S.CI.E.S-CPV High School, Mumbai, India, India, 2009

DISHALI R. KHILARI

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

To secure a challenging position in a firm where I can get wealth of opportunity to develop my skills and use my knowledge and experience in the exciting, fast-paced environment of technology. I am willing to UPGRADE myself with new set of skills which are required to become professional Software Engineer. **QA Engineer** with over 5 years+ of successful experience in Automation Testing and Manual Testing. Recognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in IT industry. Strengths in Automation and Manual backed by training in Software Testing. Pursued Masters in IT from Charles Sturt University Brisbane. Currently working with ASX as Automation Test Engineer.

SKILLS

- Tools Used: Mantis, JAVA(Maven), Basic C, Database Skills: Database, SQL, Basic C++, Selenium.
- · Eclipse, MS-Office.
- OS Used: Windows, Ubuntu, Mac-OS.
- Programming: JAVA, Python, C# C, MS-Office, C++.
- MongoDB.
- Testing tools: Bugzilla, JIRA, Testlink, Eclipse, Mantis, Jmeter, Tarantula, Selenium.
- Integration Skills: Azure, GitHub, Confluence, JIRA, Bamboo and Jenkins.
- Automation: Scripting and Manual, Selenium using Serenity BDD and Gherkin language.

WORK HISTORY

July 2021 - Current

Australian Security Exchange - Automation Test Engineer, Sydney, NSW

- · Monitored resolution of bugs, tested fixes and helped developers tackle ongoing problems by providing QA perspective.
- Documented testing procedures for developers and future testing use.
- Tested functional and compatibility of new programs or updates in comparison to existing applications.
- Authored and maintained well-organized, efficient and successful manual test cases for entire team.
- Identified and tracked defects with Automation framework and supported developers in resolving problems by completing additional tests. • Operated under Agile and Scrum frameworks to complete releases every 3 to 6 months
- and well-organized sprints. · Debugged code and located root causes of problems by reviewing configuration files
- and logs. • Performed Automation, Manual and API tests on modules and full software
- implementations for more than 3 projects per year. • Implemented use of Serenity BDD, Selenium. Gherkin, Java and Python tools to
- illustrate project features and requirements. • Demonstrated respect, friendliness and willingness to help wherever needed.
- Proved successful working within tight deadlines and fast-paced atmosphere.
- Working on Test Plan test documentation and risk based testing for Automation testing.

February 2021 - July 2021

Felix - Automation Test Analyst, Brisbane, QLD

- Completed automation of functional and regression testing.
- Established company automation methodology, frameworks and tools.
- · Updated and maintained project documentation for detailed recordkeeping.
- Identified bugs and issues within system and applied troubleshooting techniques for mitigation purposes.
- Evaluated data sets from multiple test implementations to determine and account for standard variance in test results.
- · Reviewed all test cases and test scripts for quality and identified additional areas to · Monitored emerging test automation frameworks, technologies and best practices for
- useful developments. · Identified appropriate situations for implementing test automation, accounting for situations where automated testing was counterproductive.
- Applied Agile Delivery methods to simplify testing process decisions through iterative development.
- Met with quality assurance, developers and project managers to assess scope and sequence of project.
- Created detailed test cases for use on diverse projects.

July 2020 - February 2021

Centelon Pvt.Ltd. - Testing Automation Intern, Melbourne, VIC Effectively interacted with Product team and Automation and Manual Testing [Ty

- **Automation and Manual Testing** departments regarding software defects and issues found by **automation testing** issues, working closely to develop innovative solutions. · Developed and implemented API using Json and Rest Assured for test plans and
- worked on Azure for CI/CD. · Gathered, organized and annotated data gained during testing.
- August 2017 October 2018

FlexiLoans Pvt. Ltd - Quality Analyst Engineer

Gathered data on integration issues and vulnerabilities and reported all findings,

- including improvement recommendations. • Established company automation methodology, frameworks and tools. Preparing Test
- case, Test scripts and coordinate with team accordingly. • Inspected Mobile applications testing, Website Testing, API Testing, Load Testing and
- compared against standards to meet regulatory requirements. • Scripting in java using Selenium. Worked on whole project of the company.
- Identified and resolved variances to bring products in line with requirements.

April 2016 - July 2017

Xalted Information System Pvt. Ltd - Associate Test Engineer- QA Requirement Gathering and Gap Analysis from Team.

- · Analysis and preparing Test Plan and per Test levels, Preparing Test case, Test scripts and coordinate with team accordingly.
- Efficiently executed over more than 400 types of scripts using hybrid framework.
- Scripting in java using Selenium. Worked on 6 modules for this Company.
- Tested, identified and troubleshot problems in field with cellular networks and data collection equipment.

- **CERTIFICATIONS** "Professional Software Tester Specialist" course from SQUAD InfoTech.(Mumbai, India)
 - Complete Python Programming Masterclass Beginner to Advanced. · Completed Women's Leadership level 1
 - Completed Agile Software Testing-Techniques and Tools. Completed Advance Agile Scrum Master Training.

Pursued Automation & Manual Testing.

· Preparing for ISTQB Foundation level. · Good Knowledge about JAVA, Selenium and SQL.

- ADDITIONAL INFORMATION
 - Permanent Resident of Australia. • Ready to Relocate anywhere in Australia.

HOBBIES

- I like to invest my time for self care activities like badminton, running.

Indoor activities table tennis, knitting and pottery.